const quizData = {
    ques0: {
        question: "1.What does HTML stand for ?",
        options: [
            "Hyper Tag Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Hyperlinks Text Mark Language",
            "Hyperlinking Text Marking Language",
        ],
        ans: 3,
    },
    ques1: {
        question: "2. What symbol indicates a tag ?",
        options: [
            "Angle brackets e.g.<>",
            "Curved brackets e.g. {,}",
            " Commas e.g. ','",
            "Exclamation marks e.g. !",
        ],
        ans: 1,
    },
    ques2: {
        question: "3. Which of these is a geniune tag keyword?",
        options: ["Header", "Bold", "Body", "Image"],
        ans: 3,
    },
    ques3: {
        question: "4. A CSS file can be applied to only one HTML file. ?",
        options: ["True", "False", "Maybe", "N/A"],
        ans: 2,
    },
    ques4: {
        question: "5.What is the correct tag for a line break ?",
        options: ["<br />", "</br >", "<linebr />", "<break />"],
        ans: 1,
    },
    ques5: {
        question: "6. What does CSS stand for ?",
        options: [
            "Computing Style Sheet",
            "Creative Style Sheet",
            "Cascading Style Site",
            "Cascading Style Sheet",
        ],
        ans: 4,
    },
    ques6: {
        question: "7. Where should a CSS file be referenced in a HTML file ?",
        options: [
            "Before any HTML code",
            "After any HTML code",
            "Inside the body section",
            "Inside the head section",
        ],
        ans: 4,
    },
    ques7: {
        question:
            "8.What is the correct format for aligning written content to the center of the page in CSS ?",
        options: [
            "Text-align:center;",
            "Font-align:center;",
            "Text:align-center;",
            "Font:align-center;",
        ],
        ans: 1,
    },
    ques8: {
        question:
            "9. What is the correct format for changing the background colour of a div in CSS ?",
        options: [
            "Bg-color:red;",
            "Background:red;",
            "Background-colour:red;",
            "Background-color:red;",
        ],
        ans: 4,
    },
    ques9: {
        question: "10.What is the correct format for a div ?",
        options: [
            "Div-id=example",
            'Div id="example"',
            'Div="example"',
            "Div.example",
        ],
        ans: 3,
    },
    keys: [
        "ques0",
        "ques1",
        "ques2",
        "ques3",
        "ques4",
        "ques5",
        "ques6",
        "ques7",
        "ques8",
        "ques9",
    ],
    ans: [3, 1, 3, 2, 1, 4, 4, 1, 4, 3],
};

module.exports = quizData;
